<resources>
	<string name="setclass">Set Class</string>
    <string name="characterClass">Class: </string>
	<string name="classSoldier">Soldier</string>
	<string name="classMartialArtist">Martial Artist</string>
	<string name="classGunslinger">Gunslinger</string>
	<string name="classInfiltrator">Infiltrator</string>
	<string name="classDaredevil">Daredevil</string>
	<string name="classBodyguard">Bodyguard</string>
	<string name="classFieldScientist">Field Scientist</string>
	<string name="classTechie">Techie</string>
	<string name="classFieldMedic">Field Medic</string>
	<string name="classInvestigator">Investigator</string>
	<string name="classPersonality">Personality</string>
	<string name="classNegotiator">Negotiator</string>
	<string name="classSoldierDescription">Requirements:
	\nTo qualify to become a Soldier, a character must fulfill the following criteria: base attack bonus of +3; knowledge of tactics for 3 ranks; personal firearms proficiency
	\nClass Information:
	\nHit Die: 1d10
	\nAction Points: 6 + one-half character level, rounded down, every time the character attains a new level in this class.
	\nClass Skills: The Soldier’s class skills (and the key ability for each skill) are: Demolitions (Int), Drive (Dex), Intimidate (Cha), Jump (Str), Knowledge (current events, history, popular culture, tactics) (Int), Listen (Wis), Navigate (Int), Profession (Wis), Read/Write Language (none), Speak Language (none), Spot (Wis), Survival (Wis), Swim (Str). Skill Points at Each Level: 5 + Int modifier.
	\nClass Features:
	\nWeapon Focus: At 1st level, a Soldier gains the Weapon Focus class feature, providing the benefit of the feat with the same name. The Soldier chooses a specific weapon. The soldier can choose unarmed strike or grapple as the weapon. The soldier must be proficient with the chosen weapon. The soldier adds +1 to all attack rolls made using the selected weapon.
	\nWeapon Specialization: At 2nd level, a Soldier gains weapon specialization with a specific melee or ranged weapon that he or she also has applied the Weapon Focus feat or class feature to. The soldier gets a +2 bonus on damage rolls with the chosen weapon.
	\nBonus Feats: At 3rd, 6th, and 9th level, the Soldier gets a bonus feat. The bonus feat must be selected from the following list, and the Soldier must meet all the prerequisites of the feat to select it. Advanced Firearms Proficiency, Archaic Weapons Proficiency, Armor Proficiency (light), Armor Proficiency (medium), Armor Proficiency (heavy), Brawl, Burst Fire, Cleave, Combat Reflexes, Exotic Firearms Proficiency, Exotic Melee Weapon Proficiency, Far Shot, Great Cleave, Improved Brawl, Improved Knockout Punch, Knockout Punch, Power Attack.
	\nTactical Aid: As a full-round action, the Soldier provides tactical aid to all of his allies (including himself) within sight and voice range of his position. This use of tactical aid requires an action point. This aid provides a +1 competence bonus on attack rolls. The bonus lasts for a number of rounds equal to one-half of the Soldier’s level in the advanced class, rounded down.
	\nImproved Critical: For the weapon the Soldier has applied weapon specialization to the Soldier’s threat range increases by one. 
	\nImproved Reaction: At 7th level, a Soldier gains a +2 competence bonus on initiative checks.
	\nGreater Weapon Specialization: At 8th level, a Soldier gains greater weapon specialization with the weapon he  or she selected at 2nd level. This ability increases the bonus on damage rolls to +4 when using the selected weapon.
	\nCritical Strike: At 10th level, a Soldier gains the ability to automatically confirm a threat as a critical hit when attacking with the weapon he or she has applied weapon specialization to, eliminating the need to make a roll to confirm the critical hit.
	</string>
	<string name="classMartialArtistDescription">Requirements:
	\nTo qualify to become a Martial Artist, a character must fulfill the following criteria: base attack bonus of +3; the skill to jump 3 ranks; Combat Martial Arts, Defensive Martial Arts
	\nClass Information:
	\nHit Die: 1d8 
	\nAction Points: 6 + one-half character level, rounded down, every time the martial artist attains a new level in this class.
	\nClass Skills: The Martial Artist’s class skills (and the key ability for each skill) are: Balance (Dex), Climb (Str), Escape Artist (Dex), Hide (Dex), Intimidate (Cha), Jump (Str), Knowledge (current events, popular culture, theology and philosophy) (Int), Move Silently (Dex), Perform (dance) (Cha), Profession (Wis), Read/Write Language (none), Speak Language (none), Spot (Wis), Tumble (Dex). Skill Points at Each Level: 3 + Int modifier.
	\nClass Features: The following features pertain to the Martial Artist advanced class.
	\nLiving Weapon: The Martial Artist attacks with either fist interchangeably, or even with elbows, knees, and feet. This means that the Martial Artist may even make unarmed strikes when his or her hands are full, and there is no such thing as an off-hand attack for a Martial Artist striking unarmed. The Martial Artist also deals more damage with unarmed strikes. At 1st level, the martial artist deals 1d6 points of damage with an unarmed strike. At 4th level, damage increases to 1d8. At 8th level, it increases to 1d10. This is an increase to Combat Martial Arts damage; this has no effect on Brawl.
	\nFlying Kick: Starting at 2nd level, a Martial Artist can use a charge to deliver a devastating flying kick to an opponent. At the end of this charge, the martial artist adds his or her class level as a bonus to the damage he or she deals with an unarmed strike.
	\mBonus Feats: At 3rd, 6th, and 9th level, the Martial Artist gets a bonus feat. The bonus feat must be selected from the following list, and the Martial Artist must meet all the prerequisites of the feat to select it. Acrobatic, Advanced Combat Martial Arts, Archaic Weapons Proficiency, Combat Reflexes, Combat Throw, Elusive Target, Exotic Melee Weapon Proficiency, Improved Combat Throw, Improved Combat Martial Arts, Unbalance Opponent.
	\nIron Fist: At 5th level, a Martial Artist gains the ability to spend 1 action point to increase the damage he or she deals to a single opponent with a single unarmed strike. The martial artist declares the use of the action point after making a successful unarmed strike. The result of the action point roll is added to the damage roll for that attack. At 10th level, this ability improves. The Martial Artist now adds the result of the action point roll to all successful attacks he or she makes in a round.
	\nFlurry of Blows: At 7th level, a Martial Artist gains the ability to strike with a flurry of blows at the expense of accuracy. The Martial Artist must be unarmored to use this talent, and he or she must make unarmed strikes to gain the benefit. With a flurry of blows, the Martial Artist may make one extra attack in a round at his or her highest base attack bonus. This attack and each other attack made in the round take a –2 penalty. This ability can only be used when taking the full attack action. The penalty applies to all attacks for one full round, including attacks of opportunity    
	</string>
	<string name="classGunslingerDescription">Requirements:
	\nTo qualify to become a Gunslinger, a character must fulfill the following criteria: base attack bonus of +2; six ranks of sleight of hand and tumble; Personal Firearms Proficiency.
	\nClass Information
	\nHit Die: 1d10 
	\nAction Points: 6 + one-half character level, rounded down, every time the gunslinger attains a new level in this class.
	\nClass Skills: The Gunslinger’s class skills (and the key ability for each skill) are: Bluff (Cha), Demolitions (Int), Drive (Dex), Escape Artist (Dex), Gamble (Wis), Intimidate (Cha), Knowledge (current events, popular culture, streetwise) (Int), Move Silently (Dex), Profession (Wis), Read/Write Language (none), Ride (Dex), Sleight of Hand (Dex), Speak Language (none), Spot (Wis), Survival (Wis), Tumble (Dex). Skill Points at Each Level: 5 + Int modifier.
	\nClass Features: The following features pertain to the Gunslinger advanced class.
	\nClose Combat Shot: At 1st level, a Gunslinger gains the ability to make a ranged attack with a Medium-size or smaller firearm while in a threatened area without provoking an attack of opportunity.
	\nWeapon Focus: At 2nd level, a Gunslinger gains the Weapon Focus class feature, providing the benefit of the feat with the same name. The Gunslinger must choose a specific personal firearm. The gunslinger adds +1 to all attack rolls you make using the selected personal firearm.
	\nBonus Feats: At 3rd, 6th, and 9th level, the Gunslinger gets a bonus feat. The bonus feat must be selected from the following list, and the Gunslinger must meet all the prerequisites of the feat to select it. Advanced Firearms Proficiency, Advanced Two-Weapon Fighting, Burst Fire, Dead Aim, Double Tap, Far Shot, Improved Two-Weapon Fighting, Precise Shot, Quick Draw, Quick Reload, Shot on the Run, Skip Shot, Strafe, Two-Weapon Fighting.
	\nDefensive Position: Starting at 4th level, the Gunslinger gains an additional +2 cover bonus to Defense and an additional +2 cover bonus on Reflex saves whenever he or she has one-quarter, one-half, three-quarters, or nine-tenths cover.
	\nLightning Shot: Starting at 5th level, a Gunslinger can make a flurry of ranged attacks with a personal firearm at the expense of accuracy. With a lightning shot, the Gunslinger may make one extra ranged attack with a personal firearm in a round at his or her highest base attack bonus. This attack and each other attack made in the round take a –2 penalty. This ability can only be used when taking the full attack action. The penalty applies to all attacks for one full round, including attacks of opportunity.
	\nSharp-Shooting: At 7th level, if the Gunslinger uses a personal firearm to attack a target, the cover bonus to the target’s Defense for one-quarter, one-half, three-quarters, or nine-tenths cover is reduced by 2.
	\nGreater Weapon Focus: At 8th level, a Gunslinger receives a +1 competence bonus on attack rolls made with the firearm selected for the Weapon Focus ability at 2nd level. This bonus stacks with the earlier bonus.
	\nBullseye: At 10th level, a Gunslinger becomes so adept at using the firearm to which he or she has applied Weapon Focus and Greater Weapon Focus that the gunslinger’s attacks with that firearm can deal extra damage. With a successful attack, before damage is rolled, the gunslinger can spend 1 action point to deal +3d6 points of damage.
	</string>
	<string name="classInfiltratorDescription">Requirements:
	\nTo qualify to become an Infiltrator, a character must fulfill the following criteria: base attack bonus of +2; the skills of Hiding 6 ranks and Moving Silently 6 ranks.
	\nClass Information: The following information pertains to the Infiltrator advanced class.
	\nHit Die: 1d8
	\nAction Points: 6 + one-half character level, rounded down, every time the infiltrator attains a new level in this class.
	\nClass Skills: The Infiltrator’s class skills (and the key ability for each skill) are: Balance (Dex), Climb (Str), Disable Device (Int), Disguise (Cha), Escape Artist (Dex), Hide (Dex), Investigate (Int), Jump (Str), Knowledge (art, business, current events, popular culture, streetwise) (Int), Listen (Wis), Move Silently (Dex), Profession (Wis), Read/Write Language (none), Search (Int), Sleight of Hand (Dex), Speak Language (none), Spot (Wis), Tumble (Dex). Skill Points at Each Level: 7 + Int modifier.
	\nClass Features: The following features pertain to the Infiltrator advanced class.
	\nSweep: An Infiltrator knows how to size up an area and get the lay of the land in a single sweep of his or her eyes. This sweep provides a +4 circumstance bonus on Spot checks and covers an area out to 30 feet away from the Infiltrator. The Infiltrator can use this bonus at the start of an encounter. Anything not concealed can be spotted in a sweep with a successful check (DC 10). The DC for concealed or less obvious threats is equal to their Hide check result.
	\nImprovised Implements: At 2nd level, an Infiltrator no longer takes a –4 penalty when wielding an improvised weapon. Also, the Infiltrator is able to make do without proper equipment in certain circumstances: the Infiltrator no longer takes a –4 penalty when using the Climb and Disable Device skills without the proper tools.
	\nBonus Feats: At 3rd, 6th, and 9th level, the Infiltrator gets a bonus feat. The bonus feat must be selected from the following list, and the Infiltrator must meet all the prerequisites of the feat to select it. Acrobatic, Alertness, Armor Proficiency (light), Athletic, Attentive, Brawl, Cautious, Defensive Martial Arts, Dodge, Elusive Target, Meticulous, Mobility, Nimble, Renown, Run, Stealthy.
	\nImproved Evasion: If an Infiltrator of 4th level or higher is exposed to any effect that normally allows a character to attempt a Reflex saving throw for half damage, the Infiltrator suffers no damage if he or she makes a successful saving throw and only half damage on a failed save. Improved evasion can only be used when wearing light armor or no armor. For an Infiltrator who does not have evasion (see the Fast hero class description), improved evasion counts as evasion for the purpose of meeting the prerequisites on the Fast hero’s defensive talent tree.
	\nSkill Mastery: At 5th level, an Infiltrator selects a number of skills from his or her class list equal to 3 + his or her Intelligence modifier. When making a check using one of these skills, the Infiltrator may take 10 even if stress and distractions would normally prevent him or her from doing so.
	\nImprovised Weapon Damage: At 7th level, an Infiltrator’s attacks with improvised weapons deal more damage. The Infiltrator treats an improvised weapon as one size category larger than it is for the purpose of determining the damage it deals.
	\nImproved Sweep: At 8th level, an Infiltrator’s ability to get the lay of the land improves. Now the Infiltrator not only spots potential perils with a successful check, he or she can determine the relative strength of these dangers. A successful check relates the danger’s strength compared to the Infiltrator: stronger (higher level or Hit Dice), on par (same level or HD), or weaker (lower level or HD).
	\nWithout a Trace: At 10th level, when an Infiltrator uses any of the following skills: Balance, Climb, Disable Device, Escape Artist, Hide, Move Silently, and Sleight of Hand, those using Investigate, Listen, Search, or Spot to detect the Infiltrator’s activity take a –4 penalty.
	</string>
	<string name="classDaredevilDescription">Requirements:
	\nTo qualify to become a Daredevil, a character must fulfill the following criteria: Base Attack Bonus of +2; Skills of Concentration 6 ranks, Drive 6 ranks; Feat of Endurance;
	\nClass Information: The following information pertains to the Daredevil advanced class.
	\nHit Die: 1d10 
	\nAction Points: 6 + one-half character level, rounded down, every time he or she attains a new level in this class.
	\nClass Skills: The Daredevil’s class skills (and the key ability for each skill) are: Balance (Dex), Climb (Str), Concentration (Con), Demolitions (Int), Drive (Dex), Escape Artist (Dex), Intimidate (Cha), Jump (Str), Knowledge (current events, popular culture) (Int), Perform (act) (Cha), Pilot (Dex), Profession (Wis), Read/Write Language (none), Ride (Dex), Speak Language (none), Spot (Wis), Swim (Str), Tumble (Dex). Skill Points at Each Level: 5 + Int modifier
	\nClass Features: The following features pertain to the Daredevil advanced class.
	\nFearless: A Daredevil gains a +4 morale bonus on Will saves to resist fear effects and on level checks to oppose Intimidate checks.
	\nNip-Up: A Daredevil of 2nd level or higher can stand up from a prone position as a free action that does not provoke an attack of opportunity.
	\nBonus Feats: At 3rd, 6th, and 9th level, the Daredevil gets a bonus feat. The bonus feat must be selected from the following list, and the Daredevil must meet all the prerequisites of the feat to select it. Acrobatic, Armor Proficiency (light), Armor Proficiency (medium), Athletic, Brawl, Cautious, Dodge, Force Stop, Improved Brawl, Improved Damage Threshold, Improved Knockout Punch, Knockout Punch, Mobility, Nimble, Spring Attack, Streetfighting, Surface Vehicle Operation, Toughness, Vehicle Dodge, Vehicle Expert.
	\nAction Boost: This ability, gained at 4th level, allows a Daredevil to spend 2 action points on a single action in a round. A Daredevil can spend 1 action point, see the result of the roll, and then decide to spend a second point, as long as he or she does so before the Gamemaster reveals the result of the action.
	\nAdrenaline Rush: At 5th level, a Daredevil can temporarily increase one of his or her physical ability scores (Strength, Dexterity, or Constitution). The Daredevil spends 1 action point and gets to increase the selected ability score by 1d4+1 points. The increase lasts for a number of rounds equal to his or her class level. At the end of the duration, the Daredevil is fatigued for 1d4+1 rounds. At 8th level, a Daredevil can temporarily increase two physical ability scores. At the end of the duration, the Daredevil is fatigued for 1d6+2 rounds.
	\nDelay Damage: Once per day, a Daredevil of 7th level or higher can delay the damage dealt by a single attack or effect for a number of rounds equal to his or her class level.
	\nDamage Threshold: A 10th-level Daredevil increases his or her massive damage threshold by 3 points. This increase stacks with the increase provided by the Improved Damage Threshold feat.
	</string>
</resources>		